webguide4u.com 2012-05-25

# Privacy Policy

WebGuide4U as a beginner’s guide to WordPress, Webhosting, Photoshop and Web Designing. We have more than 200+ posts which provides regular source of updates via Emails and RSS feeds. We are serious in protecting your private data. We assured you that it will only be used to support relationship with WebGuide4U. This privacy policy is intended for all users of WebGuide4U.com

By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.

On a simple note WebGuide4U.com runs with the back-end of third partners policies

  * **For Advertisements** appearing on the **WebGuide4U.com** you can refer to [**Google Adsense** privacy policies](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * **For Visitor tracking y** ou can refer to [**WordPress.com** privacy policies](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and [**GOOGLE ANALYTICS** TERMS OF SERVICE](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html)
  * **For E-mail/RSS updates** you can refer to [**Google Feedburner** Privacy Statement](http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy)

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit WebGuide4U.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Some common definition of Cookies and Log Files described above are as follows:

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a web site, is placed by the web server into the browser’s application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the web site to “recognize” you as a unique individual.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This may allow us to keep you logged automatically fill in data for you in various forms.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that WebGuide4U.com is not responsible for the privacy practices, or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Comments** ****

We love to hear more from our readers in the form of comments, but none of the comment will be entertained which is abusive, spread hatred, racial or hurts anyone opinion. All the comments are moderated to maintain the integrity of individual. Email address mentioned in the comment form will always be use for privacy and never be used for spamming. Though we highly recommend never post your Email address into the comments, so that other can’t see it. Even if you post email address in comments, make sure you follow this format **admin[at]gmail.com**.

**Advertising Policy**

To help the site expansion and to cover the cost of running the site WebGuide4U, we run some advertising on the site and uses many third-party advertisements to serve advertisement for managing this blog. Google Adsense, as a third party uses cookies to serve ads on my blog. Google uses the DART cookie to serve advertisement based on user’s interest and previous interaction. Though users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie settings by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

WebGuide4U.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice. Please check back frequently in the event of changes.

Your use of WebGuide4U.com constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
